https://www.epcrugby.com/legal/

i
Search a specific phrase by including quotation marks, example "Pick your try of the week"
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy describes how we use the information which we collect on our https://www.epcrugby.com/ website (the “website”). You do not have to give us any personal information in order to use most of our website. However, if you wish to register with us to receive the newsletter or enter competitions, you will need to provide us with certain additional information (including certain personally identifiable information).
OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY
We may obtain information about you when you use the website. We are committed to protecting your privacy during your visits to the website and recognise our responsibility to keep the information you provide to us confidential at all times.
WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
The types of information we collect includes such things as names, email addresses and such other information as you may have provided us with from time to time. If you decide to provide us with information about yourself, we may use it to send you details about ERC, the Heineken Cup, European Challenge Cup and or the services and products of our partners. We may also send you ezines or other information which we believe may be of interest to you. If at any time you do not want us to do this, please unsubscribe from our newsletter at https://www.epcrugby.com/.
We use your information to improve our marketing, for administration and to provide our services to you. It is not our practice to disclose your personal information to any other parties or for any other reason, other than as set out on this website, without your prior consent. However, from time to time we may employ the services of a third party to help us in certain areas or our business (including for example for website hosting) and in such cases that third party may receive your information – we will however continue to control the use of your information.
COOKIES
EU COOKIE DIRECTIVE
From 26 May 2011 a new European Union directive requires us to gain the consent of our users to download cookies on to their machines.
There are various methods we could use to gain users consent. For example, we could use pop-ups; prompting users to tick a box to confirm they give permission for us to download cookies on their machine.
Alternatively, we could use an online form that all users must complete before using the website.
We consider both of these solutions as obtrusive. We want our users find information and services quickly.
Therefore, we have taken the decision to promote how we use cookies on our website instead. This will enable users to make an informed decision whether they want to disable this feature.
There are links on our terms and conditions and disclaimer pages which are in the footer of every web page pointing to this information.
WHAT IS A COOKIE
Information may be sent to your computer in the form of an Internet “cookie” to allow our servers to monitor your requirements. The cookie is stored on your computer. Our server may request that your computer return a cookie to it.
These return cookies do not contain any information supplied by you or any personally identifiable information about you.
Such measures are necessary to allow EPCR to measure the usability of the systems, which will help to continually improve user experience of our websites.
Your browser software should however enable you to block cookies if you wish to. For more information about cookies, please visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/.
STRICTLY NECESSARY COOKIES
These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the website. Without these cookies services you have asked for, like shopping baskets or e-billing, cannot be provided.
PERFORMANCE COOKIES
These cookies collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how a website works.
FUNCTIONALITY COOKIES
These cookies allow the website to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features. For instance, a website may be able to provide you with local weather reports or traffic news by storing in a cookie the region in which you are currently located.
These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customise. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites.
TARGETING OR ADVERTISING COOKIES
These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are usually placed by advertising networks with the website operator’s permission. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organisations such as advertisers. Quite often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organisation.
GOOGLE ANALYTICS
EPCR uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google. Google Analytics collects first party cookies, which are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour. This information is sent to Google and is used to evaluate how our website is being used. This enables EPCR to compile statistical reports. A full list of cookies used by Google Analytics and explanations on how these work are available on the Google code website.
EPCR does not collect (nor allow any third party to collect) personally identifiable information of visitors to our site. We will not associate any data gathered with any personally identifying information. We will not link or seek to link an IP address with the identity of a computer user. In short, Google Analytics doesn’t identify who you are, but it does track your movements on our websites.
HOW TO DISABLE COOKIES
You can stop cookies being downloaded on to your computer by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.
There is more information about cookies, including how to delete them on the website aboutcookies.org. You may also opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics.
CONSENT
By using our website you consent to collection and use of any information you provide to us by EPCR Limited for the purposes described above. If we amend our privacy policy, any changes will be published on this web site. If at any time you wish to update the information which we hold about you, or if you wish to stop receiving information from EPCR, please contact us.
AMENDMENTS
We may modify, amend or replace this privacy policy from time to time at our sole discretion. If we do so then we will use our reasonably endeavours to post notice of such changes on the site.
LINKS
Our website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. This privacy policy applies only to information collected by us on our website.
SECURITY
We take all appropriate steps to protect your information both online and offline. If you would like information on our security procedures please contact us using the details that are listed on Contact us section of the site.
AMENDING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
If your personal information changes or if you no longer wish to receive our epcrugby.com ezine please email us (at the address given in the Contact Us section) and we will update and/or remove your details as soon as reasonably possible.
CONTACT US
If you have any questions about this policy please contact us by sending us an email through our contact us section.
Official Title Partner
Official Partner
Official Supporters
Broadcast Partners
Media Partners
Match Centre
x
Fixtures
Finals
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.I accept the cookies from this sitePrivacy Policy
